bidspotter.com 2002-12-11

# BidSpotter, Inc Privacy Policy

**BidSpotter, Inc. Privacy Policy**

**Introduction**   
BidSpotter, Inc. (BidSpotter.com) respects each individual’s right to personal privacy.  We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement.  This statement applies solely to information collected at BidSpotter, Inc. (BidSpotter.com)’s Web site. ** **

**Part I.   Information Collection**   
BidSpotter, Inc. (BidSpotter.com) collects information through our Web site at several points.  We collect the following information about primary visitors: (i) IP address; (ii) domain server; (iii) type of computer; and (iv) type of web browser (collectively “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Site.

In order for you to access certain services and to submit bids and purchase products being offered for bid via BidSpotter.com, we require you to provide us with information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information may include: (i) Contact Data (such as your name, mailing and e-mail addresses); (ii) Financial Data (such as your account or credit card number); and (iii) Demographic Data (such as your zip code, age and income). BidSpotter, Inc. (BidSpotter.com) does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information.

We collect this information through registration forms and automatic logging files. 

We only employ cookies on our messageboards. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user’s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable BidSpotter, Inc. (BidSpotter.com) to deliver customized content to users.  Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. 

**Part II.   Information Usage.   
**The information collected by BidSpotter, Inc. (BidSpotter.com) will be used for the bidder approval process, improvement of site navigation and communication between BidSpotter, Inc. (BidSpotter.com) and current registered users.  Users who provide information will receive email announcements and will be considered for eligibility to bid by partner auction houses. 

Registered users will receive additional announcements from us about upcoming auctions and certain enhancements to the website. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.

We may share data with the following third parties: Auction houses whose auctions you have registered to participate in.  These third parties will use the information as follows: To determine your eligibility to participate and potentially notify you of upcoming events. 

We offer links to other Web sites.  Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies.  Their standards may differ from ours.

Our Web site offers message boards.  Please be advised that information posted in these venues becomes public knowledge. 

**Part III.   Access to Information   
**  Users may access their own personal information and contact us about inaccuracies they may find.  This may be done by logging into their secure bidder area from most pages on the BidSpotter.com site.  Users may delete their information from our database by sending an email to: [Support@bidspotter.com](mailto:help@bidspotter.com). Please mention your user name, email address and first and last name.

**Part IV. Problem Resolution   
**If problems arise, users may contact BidSpotter, Inc. (BidSpotter.com) by email: [Support@bidspotter.com](mailto:help@bidspotter.com).  We are committed to resolving disputes within 48 hours.

**Part V. Data Storage and Security  
**BidSpotter, Inc. (BidSpotter.com) protects user information with the following security measures: 128 bit encryption utilized for transmission of all sensitive data, secure database placement and secure 128 bit encryption access to sensitive data by auction house partners. 

If you have any further questions about privacy or security, please contact us by sending an email to: [Support@bidspotter.com](mailto:help@bidspotter.com).
